bcbusinessonline.ca 2011-01-02

# User Agreement & Privacy Polic | BCBusiness

PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE

Privacy Policy

Canada Wide Media Limited (“Canada Wide”) respects the privacy of our customers and is committed to protecting privacy rights of identifiable individuals. In this regard, Canada Wide has prepared this Web-site privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to detail how Canada Wide collects, uses, and discloses any Personal Information collected about you on the Canada Wide web-site, [www.canadawide.com](http://www.canadawide.com/ "www.canadawide.com") (the “Web-site”).

Canada Wide, and/or its affiliates and subsidiaries, is the owner and operator of various self-owned magazines, books, custom publications, e-newsletters, directories, and web-sites, including without limitation, [www.bcbusinessonline.ca](http://www.bcbusinessonline.ca/ "www.bcbusinessonline.ca"), [www.gardenwiseonline.ca](http://www.gardenwiseonline.ca/ "www.gardenwiseonline.ca"), [www.granvilleonline.ca](http://www.granvilleonline.ca/ "www.granvilleonline.ca"), and [www.tvweekonline.ca](http://www.tvweekonline.ca/ "www.tvweekonline.ca") (collectively, the “Affiliates”).

The Privacy Policy has been created to inform our customers and all visitors to the Web-site of the manner in which Canada Wide maintains the confidentiality of your Personal Information and to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.

The Privacy Policy for the Web-site sets out the following:

•    What is “Personal Information”?  
•    Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information  
•    Your Consent to Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information  
•    Use of Technology on the Web-site  
•    Links to Other Web-sites  
•    Security of Personal Information  
•    Requests for Access to Personal Information  
•    Requests for Correction of Personal Information  
•    Contacting or Communicating with Us

What is “Personal Information”?

Your “personal information” as defined at law, including without limitation, as defined under the Personal Information Protection Act of British Columbia, as amended from time to time (the “Act”), means all information about an identifiable individual (“Personal Information”). This Personal Information means information that can identify an individual (for example, your name, home telephone number, personal mobile telephone number, home address, personal email address, personal fax number, social insurance number, driver’s licence number, physical description, and credit card or other financial information specifically about you). However, Personal Information does not include business “contact information”, which is defined under the Act as information to enable an individual at a place of business to be contacted for business purposes, such as name, position name or title, business telephone number, business mobile telephone number, business address, business email, or business fax number of an individual.

Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information

Canada Wide collects, uses, and discloses your Personal Information obtained on the Web-site for itself and on behalf of its Affiliates solely for the following specified purposes:

•    To inform you of the arrival of various new products and services available from Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time, including without limitation, various new magazines and custom publications from Canada Wide.  
•    To inform you of various contests, discounts, special offers, sales, and promotions offered by Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time.  
•    To inform you of special events hosted or sponsored by Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time.  
•    To provide you with any email, print, or other newsletters, online news releases, and publications of Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time.  
•    To inform you of customer satisfaction surveys and sales surveys of Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time.  
•    To advise you any of changes or alterations to the terms of service, policies, or features of Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time, including without limitation, the terms of use of the Web-site and the Privacy Policy.  
•    To respond to your inquiries and communicate with you in connection with Canada Wide, its Affiliates, the Web-site, and the Privacy Policy.

Canada Wide will share any Personal Information obtained from you on the Web-site or otherwise only with its Affiliates. **You should be aware that Canada Wide will not share or sell your Personal Information to any third parties or organizations other than its Affiliates.** Canada Wide may communicate with you by email, mail, and various other means of communication for the specific purposes set out above.

Your Consent to Our Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal Information

By using the Web-site to register with Canada Wide, you expressly acknowledge that you will be providing Personal Information to Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time, and therefore you voluntarily consent to collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information by Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time for the specific purposes set out in the Privacy Policy. You acknowledge that Canada Wide and its Affiliates may disclose your Personal Information without your consent if required by law and in accordance any applicable exceptions under the Act.

The Web-site is directed for use by adults and Canada Wide does not knowingly collect, use, or disclose any Personal Information from children without the consent of parents. Canada Wide requests that parents monitor their children’s use of the Web-site and to contact Canada Wide in the event of any such usage by children.

If you have provided your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information by Canada Wide and its Affiliates from time to time under this Privacy Policy, you may, at any time, withdraw your consent, unsubscribe, and request to decline to have your Personal Information collected, used, or disclosed for any or all of the specific purposes set out in the Privacy Policy. Please refer to “Contacting or Communicating with Us” of the Privacy Policy below in connection with the withdrawal of your consent.

Use of Technology on the Web-site

In order to enhance your shopping and personalize your interactive experience, the Web-site uses “cookie” technology. A “cookie” is a small bit of data that gets stored your computer. Like many commercial Web-sites, we automatically collect other information by way of electronic means, using “cookies” which are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our products and services. This information includes the address (or “URL”) of the Web-site that you came from before visiting the Web-site, which web pages you visit on the Web-site, which browser software you use to view the Web-site, your IP address, and any search terms you have entered on the Web-site or in order to access the Web-site. This data is not used individually, but is aggregated and only used to tailor the Web-site to better meet your interests and preferences. Most browsers automatically accept “cookies”, but you can usually refuse “cookies”, or selectively accept “cookies”, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn “cookies” off, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you.

In addition, Canada Wide uses third-party advertising companies, including without limitation, Google AdSense, which uses Google DoubleClick DART “cookies” to enable certain interest-based advertisements on the Web-site and the Affiliates. These third-parties may use information that is not Personal Information about your visits to the Web-site, the Affiliates, and other web-sites in order to provide interest-based advertisements about goods and services which may be of interest to you. You may opt out of the use of Google DoubleClick DART “cookies” at any time by opting out at <http://www.google.ca/intl/en/privacy_ads.html>.

Links to Other Web-sites

The Web-site may contain links to other web-sites that may or may not be the Affiliates of Canada Wide from time to time. Any such links are not intended to be referrals by Canada Wide and are posted for the purposes of convenience only. You acknowledge that Canada Wide has no responsibility, liability, or obligation to control or maintain the web-sites you visit via such links. You should ensure that you familiarize yourself with the applicable privacy policies and terms of use of all other web-sites before using the same.

Security of Personal Information

Canada Wide and its Affiliates are committed to adopting and maintaining appropriate measures and safeguards to ensure the confidentiality of your Personal Information and to protect against any loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, copying, use, modification, or disclosure. Canada Wide exercises care in the secure transmission of your Personal Information; however, no transmission of Personal Information over the Internet is 100% secure. Canada Wide is unable to guarantee that Personal Information collected, used, or disclosed through the medium of the Internet cannot be intercepted by third parties.

Requests for Access to Personal Information

The Act permits individuals to submit written requests to us to provide them with:

•    their Personal Information under our custody or control;  
•    information about how their Personal Information under our control has been and is being used by us; and  
•    the names of the individuals and organizations to whom their Personal Information under our control has been disclosed by us.  
Canada Wide will respond to requests in the time allowed by the Act and will make a reasonable effort to assist applicants and to respond as accurately and completely as reasonably possible. All requests may be subject to any fees and disbursements the law permits us to charge.

Requests for Correction of Personal Information

The Act permits individuals to submit written requests to us to correct errors or omissions in their personal information that is in our custody or control. Canada Wide will:

•    correct the personal information and, if reasonable to do so, send correction notifications to any other organizations to whom we disclosed the incorrect information; or  
•    decide not to correct the personal information, but annotate the personal information that a correction was requested but not made.

Contacting or Communicating with Us

If you have any questions with respect to the Privacy Policy concerning the handling of your Personal Information, wish to withdraw your consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of your Personal Information, or if you wish to request access to, or correction of, your Personal Information under our care and control, please contact our Privacy Officer at:

Privacy Officer  
Canada Wide Media Limited  
4th Floor, 4180 Lougheed Highway,  
Burnaby, B.C.  
Canada V5C 6A7

If you are dissatisfied with our handling of your personal information, we invite you to contact our Privacy Officer in writing, setting out the reasons for your concern. If, after our Privacy Officer has reviewed and responded to your concern, you remain dissatisfied, you may wish to contact the Office of the Information and Privacy Commissioner for British Columbia at:

P.O. Box 9038, Stn. Prov. Govt.,  
Victoria, B.C.,  
Canada V8W 9A4  
Telephone: (250) 387-5629  
Fax: (250) 387-1696  
Email: [info@oipc.bc.ca](mailto:info@oipc.bc.ca)  
Web Site: [www.oipc.bc.ca](http://www.oipc.bc.ca/ "www.oipc.bc.ca")

CANADAWIDE.COM TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT

Acceptance of Terms of Use

PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THIS WEB-SITE OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL CONTAINED ON THIS WEB-SITE IS SUBJECT AT ALL TIMES TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. Canada Wide Media Limited, c/o 4th Floor, 4180 Lougheed Highway, Burnaby, B.C. V5C 6A7 (“Canada Wide”) owns and operates this web-site, located at [http://www.bcbusinessonline.ca](http://www.bcbusinessonline.ca/ "http://www.bcbusinessonline.ca") (the “Web-site”). This Terms of Use Agreement (the “Agreement”) states the terms and conditions under which you may access and use the Web-site. By accessing and using the Web-site, you are indicating your acceptance to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Agreement. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, you must not access or use the Web-site. If you are dissatisfied with the terms, conditions, rules, policies, guidelines, or practices of Canada Wide operating the Web-site, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using it. Canada Wide may revise or amend the Agreement from time to time and at any time by updating this posting. Your use of the Web-site after any such revisions or amendments are posted shall signify your agreement to be bound by the revised or amended terms and conditions. You should visit this page on the Web-site periodically to review this Agreement, as so revised or amended from time to time.

Disclaimer of Warranties

The Web-site and all content and information contained herein, including without limitation, all text, graphics, links or other items, is provided on an “as is”, “where is”, and “as available” basis. By accessing and using the Web-site you acknowledge and agree that the use of the Web-site and the content and information provided on the Web-site is entirely at your own risk.

To the fullest extent permitted by law, Canada Wide makes no representations or warranties of any kind, implied, express, or statutory that any content or information will be accurate, complete, reliable, suitable or timely, including without limitation, any and all representations or warranties of title, that any content or information, data, software, product, service, or resources contained in or made available through the Web-site will be of merchantable quality or fit for a particular purpose, of freedom from computer viruses or harmful components and non-infringement of third-party rights, that the operation of the Web-site will be uninterrupted or error free, that defects or errors in the Web-site will be corrected, and that communications to or from the Web-site will be secure or not intercepted.

No Advice

By accessing and using the Web-site you acknowledge and agree that that any content or information in respect of this Web-site or the content or information, data, graphics, maps, software, product, service, and resources contained in or made available through the Web-site (collectively, the “Information”) is for informational purposes only. The Information is not intended to provide legal, accounting, tax, investment, financial planning, brokerage, banking, or any or other form of advice to you and in no event should you rely upon the Information to provide any such advice. Canada Wide does not represent or warrant the accuracy, adequacy, or completeness of the Information provided on the Web-site and expressly disclaims liability for any errors or omissions that may be contained in the Information. It is the responsibility of the user to perform proper due diligence before acting upon any of the Information provided.

Limitation of Liability

To the fullest extent permitted by law, neither Canada Wide nor any of its affiliates, subsidiaries, shareholders, directors, officers, employees, independent contractors, agents, successors, and assigns shall be liable for any damages of any kind, including without limitation, direct or indirect, special, incidental, punitive, or consequential damages, losses or expenses arising in connection with the Web-site or with the use of the Information, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation the use or inability to use the Web-site by any party, the failure to perform, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus or line or system failure, loss of profit or income. This limitation of liability shall apply notwithstanding Canada Wide or any of its affiliates, subsidiaries, shareholders, directors, officers, employees, independent contractors, agents, successors, and assigns being advised of the possibility or potential of such damages, losses, or expenses. Hyperlinks, links to third-party web-sites, and references to other internet resources are provided and used at the sole risk of the party accessing the Web-site and your attention is drawn to the fact that the content, accuracy, opinions expressed, together with other links provided by these resources are not investigated, verified, monitored, or endorsed by Canada Wide or any of its affiliates, subsidiaries, shareholders, directors, officers, employees, independent contractors, agents, successors, and assigns in any manner whatsoever.

Public Information

Some of the materials and information contained in the Web-site (the “Site Contents”) have been produced and published by Canada Wide from publicly available information (“Public Information”) and the Site Contents are not a substitute for a detailed investigation or analysis on a particular issue and may not always be current. The Site Contents may contain technical or other inaccuracies, omissions, or other errors, for which Canada Wide shall assume no responsibility. Neither Canada Wide nor any company whose Public Information is used on the Web-site warrants or makes any representations regarding the use, validity, quality, accuracy, completeness, or reliability of any claims, statements, or information forming part of the Site Contents. Under no circumstances, including without limitation, negligence, shall Canada Wide nor any company whose Public Information is used on the Web-site be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental, consequential, or other damages, including without limitation, any loss of profits, whether or not advised of the possibility of damage, arising from your reliance on or your use, or your inability to use, any of the Site Contents.

Ownership of Intellectual Property

By accessing and using the Web-site you acknowledge and agree that all intellectual property, including without limitation trade-marks, marks, logos, trade names, business names, service marks, copyright, and all other rights used or embodied in the Web-site are and will remain the sole property of Canada Wide. All of the Information and material supplied by Canada Wide, constitutes part of Canada Wide’s confidential and proprietary information and no party accessing the Web-site may reproduce, copy, reverse engineer, or disclose such information without the prior written consent of Canada Wide. No party accessing the Web-site may attempt to tamper with, modify, reverse engineer, gain unauthorized access to, or in any way alter any software comprised or contained in the Web-site.

You may only use the Information retrieved from the Web-site for your own personal and non-commercial purposes while accessing our services. You may not copy, distribute or redistribute the Information, including by caching, framing or similar means or sell, resell, re-transmit, transfer, assign, or otherwise make the Information retrieved from our services available in any manner to any third-party. You may not store the Information for the purposes of creating a historical database or historical data product.

Governing Law

In the event of any dispute arising in connection with the Web-site, such dispute shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of British Columbia, Canada and any party accessing and using the Web-site agrees to submit to the jurisdiction of the Province of British Columbia, Canada.

Comments  
Note: Canada Wide Media Limited is not responsible for and does not necessarily endorse the content of any of the views or opinions expressed or posted. By submitting your comments, you acknowledge and agree that Canada Wide Media Limited has the right to reproduce, broadcast, publish, and publicize those comments or any part thereof in any manner whatsoever in accordance with our Submissions Policy.
